now i am going to take this down but i just want to point out to you all that it is not just i know
jordy it's not just bots that get out of pocket this is sonja son who's an actress she's an
actress she was on the show the wire telling me i need to sit this one the fuck out for informing
folks about the ways in which the ruling class uses bread and circuses and sonja i said it here
in writing but i'm gonna say it here for you clearly you played a cop on tv do not ever think
it is your place to come in my comments to police me this is simply representative of your
incapacity for understanding concepts beyond the identity politics that make you feel comfortable
take that fist down because you're not standing for anything except for consumption
and representation which is actually assimilation and compliance now go learn your fucking lines for
your next audition